Henry Allen Moe Papers 1920-1975 Mss.B.M722
American Philosophical Society
- Henry Allen Moe Papers, 1920-1975; 120 lin. feet (Box 1-344)
  - Blossom, Sumner
  - Blum, Harold F
  - Blum, John A
  - Blum, Robert
  - Blume, Franklyn L
  - Blumer, Herbert
  - Boak, Arthur E R
  - Board of Consultants for Agriculture
  - Board of Cooperative Educational Services
  - Boardman, Anne [Mrs. Francis]
  - Boardman, Dorothy
  - Boardman, Francis
  - Boardman, Francis, Jr.
  - Boardman, James
  - Boardman, Robert C
  - Boardman, William H
  - Boas, Franz
  - Boas, George
  - Bode, Carl
  - Bodleian Library, Oxford University
  - Bodley's American Friends
  - Boe, John
  - Boehr, John W
  - Bogard, Travis
  - Bogart, L
  - Boggs, S W
  - Bohr, Niels
  - Bohs, Aye
  - Boland, Betty Lloyd [Mrs. John]
  - Boland, John D
  - Boller, Leo A
  - Bolshaw, H
  - Bolton, Herbert
  - Bolton, Theodore
  - Bombal, Maria L
  - Bomhard, Moritz
  - Bondi, Inge
  - Bone, L W
  - Bonner, John
  - Book reviews
  - Booth, John E
  - Bopp, Karl R
  - Borah, Woodrow
  - Bordley, James, III
  - Borges, Jorge Luis
  - Borghese, G A
  - Boring, Edwin G
  - Born, Katharine
  - Bosworth, Boardman M
  - Bottje, Will Gay
  - Boucher
  - Boulanger, Nadia
  - Bovenizer, George W
  - Bourne vs. Keane (Memo)
  - Bowers, F
  - Bowie, Marguerite
  - Bowles, Chester
  - Bowles, Gordon T
  - Bowman, Claude C
  - Bowman, Isaiah
  - Bowra, Maurice
  - Boyd, Mrs. Francis T
  - Boyd, George Edward
  - Boyd, Julian Parks
  - Boyd, William C
  - Boyd-Bowman, Peter
  - Boyden, Frank L
  - Boyer, Allston
  - Boyer, Francis
  - Boyer, Thomas P
  - Brademas, John
  - Braden, Thomas W
  - Bradly, Edward
  - Braider, Donald
  - Braley, Ronald W
  - Branch, Houston
  - Brandt, Joseph A
  - Brandt, Raymond P
  - Brasenose College, Oxford University
  - Brasenose College Charitable Foundation
  - Braxton, Carter M
  - Bray, Mrs. H R
  - Bray, Sir Jocelyn
  - Brebner, J Bartlett
  - Brecker, Richard L
  - Bree, Germaine
  - Breed, William B, Jr.
  - Brennan, Francis
  - Brennan, H J
  - Brennan, William J
  - Brentano's
  - Brereton, Mrs. Harmar
  - Breteau, Denise
  - Brett, George M
  - Brettel, H W
  - Brickell, Herschel
  - Brickell, Norma and Herschel
  - Bridegroom, Bruce
  - Bridenbaugh, Carl
  - Bridges, Lord
  - Bridgman, Donald E
  - Brigante, Louis
  - Bright, Mabel
  - Brims, David
  - Brinton, Crane
  - Brinton, Henry
  - Bristol, M A
  - Brittingham, Thomas E, Jr.
  - Broad Jump
  - Brockington, Dorothea
  - Brode, Wallace R
  - Brodie, Mrs. Donald
  - Broek, Jan O M
  - Bronk, Detlev W
  - Brookings Institution
  - Brooklyn Museum
  - Brooks, Chandler McC
  - Brooks, Ernest, Jr.
  - Brooks, R P
  - Brooks, Sumner C
  - Brophy, Michael D
  - Brorby, Melvin
  - Brosnan, Robert E
  - Broughton, Ann and Philip S
  - Broughton, Philip S
  - Brown, Arnold
  - Brown Brothers
  - Brown, Frank E
  - Brown, Gerald
  - Brown, Harold
  - Brown, Howard J
  - Brown, J A
  - Brown, John Mason
  - Brown, Lee
  - Brown, Mrs. Lee
  - Brown, Myra
  - Brown, Peter
  - Brown, Robert Minge
  - Brown, Ruth
  - Brown, Sterling
  - Brown University
  - Brownell, Baker
  - Brownlee, John
  - Brown's Hotel
  - Bruce, Edward
  - Bruck, Porter
  - Bruere, Henry
  - Brunauer, Esther Caukin
  - Brundage, Story and Rose
  - Bruner, Richard W (re Ralph Bunche)
  - Bryan, George
  - Bryan, Wilhelmus B
  - Bryan-Brown, A N
  - Brynner, Irena
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew
  - Buchanan, Marjory C
  - Buchanan, Norman
  - Buchinger, Maria
  - Büchler, Marie A
  - Buchner, François
  - Buck, Paul H
  - Buckley, Charles A
  - Buckley, J Z
  - Budget letters
  - Buechner, Thomas S
  - Bufano, Joseph
  - Bullard, R L
  - Bullock, Alan
  - Bullock, Calvin
  - Bullock, Marie [Mrs. Hugh]
  - Bullock, Hugh
  - Bunche, Ralph J
  - Burch, Edward
  - Burden, Douglas
  - Burden, William A M
  - Burdick, C Lalor
  - Burgess, Ernest M
  - Burgess, Stephen
  - Burhoe, Ralph W
  - Burke, S P
  - Burkhardt, Frederick
  - Burkly, Andrew
  - Burlingame, Le Roy
  - Burney, Leory E
  - Burns, Arthur F
  - Burris, Andrew M
  - Burton, John
  - Burwell, W R
  - Buschiazzo, M J
  - Bush, Martin H
  - Bush-Brown, Albert
  - Buss, Hattie [Mrs. George Edward]
  - Bustinza, F
  - Butcher, Leslie
  - Butcher, Mrs. Willard C
  - Butler, Agnes [Mrs. Clyde]
  - Butler, Ann
  - Butler, John Ben
  - Buttenheim, Harold S
  - Butterfield, Alfred
  - Butterfield, Daniel
  - Butterfield, Herbert
  - Butterfield, Kay [Mrs. Victor]
  - Butterfield, Lyman H
  - Butterfield, Roger
  - Butterfield, Victor
  - Butterworth, Doris
  - Butterworth, J A
  - Butterworth, Mrs. John
  - Buzziazo, Mario
  - Byard, Dever S
  - Byles, Louisa
  - Byrnes, James F
  - Byrnes, Robert F
  - Caballero, Diego Dominguez
  - Caballero-Escovar, Alfredo
  - Cable Arts Foundation
  - Cable, Susan
  - Cabrera, Enrique
  - Cafurro, Rafael
  - Cahn, Edmond
  - Cain, Julian
  - Cain, Walker O
  - Cairns, Huntington
  - Calandra, Alexander
  - Caldwell, Katherine Field [Mrs. James]
  - Caldwell, Robert G
  - Caliver, Ambrose
  - Calkins, Robert D
  - Callahan, John F
  - Callisen, Sterling A
  - Calmon, Pedro
  - Calvert, James
  - Calvin, Melvin
  - Camara, Augusto
  - Cameron, Kenneth Neill
  - Cameron, Rondo
  - Camfield, William A
  - Camp, R W
  - Campbell, Charles I
  - Campbell, Colin G
  - Campbell, Harold G.
  - Campbell, Mrs. James
  - Campbell, Ruth
  - Campinas
  - Campos, Armando
  - Canal Museum
  - Canessa, Mitzy
  - Cannon, Frances D [Mrs. Joe E]
  - Cannon, Roger
  - Cannon, Walter B
  - Cantan-Rose Institute of Art
  - Cantril, Hadley
  - Capezio Dance Award
  - Caplan, Harry
  - Capps, Edward
  - CAPS [Creative Artists Public Service Program]
  - Carey, E A
  - Carey, Hugh L
  - Carey, Mrs. Melbert B., Jr.
  - Carey, Walter
  - Carl Ruff Associates
  - Carlson, Edward E
  - Carlton, Mrs. Margaret
  - Carman, Harry J
  - Carman, Ofelia
  - Carmer, Carl
  - Carmichael, Leonard
  - Carmichael, Oliver C
  - Carmichael, Peter A
  - Carnegie Corporation
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington
  - Carr, William
  - Carrell, Jeptha J
  - Carrington, Noel
  - Carroll, Mark
  - Carter, Albert E
  - Carter, Bayard
  - Carter, Boyd G
  - Carter, Charles W, Jr.
  - Carter, Edward C
  - Carter, Esther Flint (Mrs.)
  - Carter, Nicholas
  - Cartwright, W A
  - Casals, Pablo
  - Case, Everett
  - Case, James H
  - Caso, Alfonso
  - Casson, James and Judith
  - Casson, Lionel
  - Casson, Stanley
  - Castell & Son, Ltd.
  - Castellon, Federico
  - Castilejo, José
  - Castro, Americo
  - Castro de Gainza Paz, Elvira
  - Cater, Douglas
  - Catgut Acoustical Society
  - Catgut Acoustical Society Newsletter
  - Catholic Art Association
  - Cattaui, Maris (Mrs.)
  - Cavanaugh, W T
  - Cawthorne, Terence
  - Center for Family Planning Program Development
  - Center for Research on Conflict Resolution
  - Center of American Living, Inc.
  - Centre Cultural International de Royaumont
  - Century Association
    - Address by Royal Cortissoz
    - Admissions
    - Bequest Committee
    - Biddle, Livingston L, Jr.
    - Board of Management
    - Building
    - Bunnell, Peter C
    - Celebration, 1941
    - Centennial
    - Centennial Fund
    - Centennial Preparations
    - Committee on Admissions
    - Committee on Exhibitions
    - Committee on Investments
    - Dinner menu, Felton
    - Endowment Fund
    - Entertainment
    - Gifts
    - Haskins, George C
    - Lawson-Johnston, Peter
    - Lake, Gerald K
    - Mahonri Fund
    - Matters of Legal Consequence
    - Meeting in honor of Nicholas Murray Butler
    - Meeting in honor of Veterans of World War II
    - Memberships
    - Memorials
    - Merrymount Press
    - Newton, Carl E
    - Nomination Committee
    - Obituaries
    - Parsons, Geoffrey
    - Sweeney, Séan
    - Setton, Kenneth
    - Szarkowski, John
    - Tarkington Citation
    - Vintage Festival
    - Wine Committee
    - Wine list
  - Cernuschi, Felix
  - Chadbourne, William M
  - Chadwell, H Marshall
  - Chagas, Carlos
  - Chagnon, Napoleon A.
  - Challener, Richard D
  - Chalmers, Gordon K
  - Chamber of Commerce, New York State
  - Chamberlain, John
  - Chamberlain, Joseph P
  - Chambers, Mrs. Robert
  - Champion, George
  - Chance, Britton
  - Chandler, Robert F, Jr.
  - Chandler, Mrs. Robert
  - Chaney, Ralph W
  - Chapelbrook Foundation
  - Chapin, Barton, Jr.
  - Chapman, Angeline C
  - Chapman, Bettina (Mrs. John W)
  - Chapman, Douglas W
  - Chapman, Gilbert W
  - Chapman, Mrs. Gilbert W
  - Chapman, Joseph M
  - Chapman, William McK
  - Chapoutier & Cie
  - Charlot, Jean
  - Chase, David
  - Chase, Harry Woodburn
  - Chastain, Judson
  - Chastain, Susan Van Fossen
  - Chauncey, Henry
  - Chaves, José M
  - Chavez, Augustin Velazquez
  - Chavez-Molino, Fernando
  - Cheek, Leslie
  - Chern, S S
  - Cherniss, Harold
  - Cherrington, Ben M
  - Cheston, George M
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St.Paul, and Pacific Railroad Company
  - Chidester, F E
  - Chief Signal Officer, U.S. Army
  - Chien, Godfrey Joseph
  - Child Welfare League
  - Children's Art Carnival
  - Childs, Richard S
  - Chile-American Association
  - Chile, etc. (Universidad Catolica)
  - Chinard, Gilbert
  - Choate, Robert
  - Chorley, Kenneth
  - Christ-Janer, Albert
  - Christensen, Asher N
  - Christian, Henry A
  - Christie, Ernest J
  - Christopherson, Paul
  - Chrystie, Thomas Witter
  - Church, Henry
  - Cintas Foundation
  - Citicorp
  - City Center of Music and Drama, Inc.
  - Claerndon, James P
  - Clan Buchanan
  - Clapp, Frederick Mortimer
  - Clark, Alfred Corning
  - Clark, Mrs. Alfred Corning
  - Clark, Arnold F
  - Clark, Dean
  - Clark, Evans
  - Clark, F Ambrose
  - Clark, Francis G
  - Clark, Henry T, Jr.
  - Clark, Jane
  - Clark, John M
  - Clark, Louis L
  - Clark, Paul F
  - Clark, Stephen C.
  - Clark, Stephen C. Biological Field Station
    - Estate
    - Memorials and related correspondence
  - Clark, Stephen C., Jr.
  - Clark, Stephen Carlton-Mary Imogene Bassett Hospital
  - Clark, Stephen C.-New York State Historical Association
  - Clark, Susan Vanderpoel (Mrs. Stephen C. Clark)
  - Clark Foundation
  - Clark University
  - Clarke, E T
  - Clarke, Gilmore D
  - Clarke, Hans T
  - Clarke-Hall, Justin
  - Claxton, Brooke
  - Cleave, Lucy
  - Clee, Gilbert Harrison
  - Cleland, Ralph E
  - Cleland, Thomas M
  - Clemens, Cyril
  - Clement, A C
  - Cleveland, Harlan
  - Cleveland Orchestra, Committee to preserve the
  - Clift, David H
  - Clinchy, Everett R
  - Cloon, William G
  - Clough, De Witt
  - Coates, L D
  - Cobb, Candler
  - Cobe, H M
  - Coburn, John B
  - Coffin, Vincent Brown
  - Coggeshall, Lowell T
  - Cohen, Harold L
  - Cohen, Morris R
  - Cohn, Alfred E
  - Coile, E J
  - Coit, Dorothy
  - Coit, Laura H
  - Colacicchi, Giovanni
  - Coldwell-Philadelphia Lawn Mower Co.
  - Cole, Helen Reid
  - Cole, Rufus S
  - Coleman, Frederick S
  - Coleman, Laurence Vail
  - Coleman-Norton, P R
  - Colgate Rochester Divinity School
  - Colin, Ralph
  - Colle, Alfred
  - College of Charleston, S. C.
  - College of William and Mary
  - College Teachers
  - Collett, Merrill J
  - Collier, Charles
  - Collier, Mrs. Nina
  - Collingridge, Alan
  - Collins, W Leighton
  - Columbia Studios
  - Columbia University
  - Columbia University Art Center
    - Bicentennial
    - Book store
    - Draft of committee report to faculty of law
    - Report of committee on selection of students
    - Social Science of Science
  - Colwell, David G
  - Comhaire-Sylvain, Suzanne
  - Comine, Margaret
  - Commager, Henry S
  - Commencement address - Southern Illinois University
  - Committee for Inter-American Artistic and Intellectual Relations
  - Committee for Inter-American Cultural Affairs
  - Committee for Islamic Culture
  - Committee for the Devense of the Constitution
  - Communications with secretaries
  - Compton, Mrs. Betty
  - Conable, Barber
  - Concerned Citizens for the Arts
  - Concha, Carlos
  - Condominas, Georges
  - Conklin, William
  - Conkwright, P J, Jr.
  - Connay, W E
  - Connecticut Commission on the Arts
  - Connecticut. Governor's Commission on Services and Expenditures
  - Connecticut Land Use
  - Connelly, Marc
  - Connor, Franklin G
  - Connor, John T
  - Conolly, Richard L
  - Conrow, Wilford S
  - Conservation of Human Resources
  - Constantine, Mildred
  - Constellation Library
  - Consular Law Society
  - Contreras, Arias A
  - Contreras, Carlos
  - Coolidge, Charles
  - Coolidge, Harold J
  - Coolidge, Jane (Mrs. Charles)
  - Cook, Charles
  - Cook, H. C., Company
  - Cook, Howard
  - Cook, Peter Geoffrey
  - Cook, Robert C
  - Cook, Russell Ames
  - Cook, Sherburne F
  - Cooke, Horace B
  - Cooksey, Donald
  - Cookson, Frank B
  - Cooledge, Jane and Cal
  - Coomeraswamy, Luisa
  - Coon, Carleton S
  - Cooper, Henry S F
  - Cooper, John M
  - Cooper Union
  - Cooperstown Museums
  - Cooperstown Graduate Programss
  - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
    See also: Executive Office of the President. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
  - Copland, Aaron
  - Coppedge, Walter R
  - Copyright Division, Library of Congress
  - Cordero Roque
  - Cordier, Andrew W
  - Coremans, Paul
  - Corey, Albert B
  - Corey, Andrew
  - Cori, Carl and Anne
  - Corner, Mrs. Betsy
  - Corner, George Washington
  - Cornish School Foundation
  - Cornwell, Dean
  - Cornwell, Mrs. Dean
  - Cornwell, F J
  - Correa de Azevedo, Luis Heitor
  - Correll, Donovan S
  - Correspondent, The
  - Corry, Andrew V
  - Cortelyou, George B
  - Cortissoz, Royal
  - Cosgrave, John O'Hara
  - Cosmos Club
  - Costigan, Mrs. Peter J
  - Costine, David
  - Cottrell, G W, Jr.
  - Coughlin, Jack
  - Council of National Defense
  - Courlander, Harold
  - Cournand, André
  - Cournand, Ruth
  - Cousins, Norman
  - Covarrubias, Miguel
  - Cowan, Clyde L
  - Cowley, Malcolm
  - Cowley, Mrs. Malcolm
  - Cowling, Donald G
  - Cox, Allyn
  - Cox Committee
  - Cox, Gardner
  - Cox, Isaac J
  - Cox, Oscar
  - Cox, Robert
  - Cox Sons and Vining
  - Coykendall, Frederick
  - Coyle, Irene M
  - Cozzens, James Gould
  - Craig, Gordon
  - Craig, Howard Reid
  - Craig, Martin
  - Cranberg, Lawrence
  - Crane, Hart
  - Crane, Josephine
  - Crane, John O
  - Crasnoff, Victor N
  - Crawford, Ralston
  - Crawford, Mrs. W L
  - Crawford, W Rex
  - Creative Artists Program Services, Inc.
  - Creative Artists Public Service Program
  - Creel, Dana S
  - Creese, James
  - Creighton, Mrs. Gwen
  - Creston, Paul
  - Crist, Raymond E
  - Crittenden, Walter H
  - Crockett, David C
  - Cronbach, Robert
  - Cronkhite, Leonard W
  - Cronkhite, Ray
  - Crosby, Madeleine
  - Crosby, Sumner McK
  - Cross-Country and Alpine Skiing
  - Crossette, George
  - Crum & Forster
  - Csapo, Arpad I
  - Cuatrecasas, Jose
  - Cuesta, Ernesto
  - Culler, George D
  - Culmee, Carlton
  - Cultural Council Foundation
  - Cummings, Herbert J
  - Cuneo, Ernest L
  - Cunningham, C C
  - Cunningham, Raymond
  - Curley, Matthew H
  - Curran, Jean A, Jr.
  - Curriculum Conference of School Administrators
  - Curtis, Charles W
  - Curtis, John S
  - Curtis, Thomas E
  - Customs House, NYC
  - Cutler, Robert
  - Cuttino, George P
  - Cuyo, University of
  - Cyert, R M
  - Cyr, Frank W
  - Dahl, Harold J
  - Dahl, Robert Alan
  - Dahlerup, Baroness Alma
  - Dalton, Charles R
  - Dalton, Jack
  - D'Amico, Victor
  - Damrosch, Douglas Stanton
  - Dana, Clinton G
  - Dana, Mrs. Dorothy
  - Dana, Richard H
  - Danbury State College
  - Danes, Gibson A
  - D'Angelo, Armand
  - Daniel, Mell
  - Daniels, Farrington
  - Daniels, Henry B
  - Daniels, John
  - Daniels, Mabel
  - Dansereau, Pierre
  - Darden, Colgate W
  - Da Rocha Lima, H
  - Darrow, Karl K
  - Dart, Raymond A
  - Dartmouth College
  - Daugherty, Robert
  - Daugherty, Mrs. Helen [Robert]
  - Daugherty, Mrs. Helen [William E.]
  - Davenport, Horace
  - Davenport, Russell W
  - Davenport, W M
  - Davidson, Jacques
  - Davidson, Marshall
  - Davidson, Ralph K
  - Davidson, Sidney
  - Davidson, W F
  - Davis, Arthur Kyle
  - Davis, Curtis W
  - Davis, David M
  - Davis, Elmer
  - Davis, Hallie Flanagan
  - Davis, Herbert
  - Davis, John H
  - Davis, R R
  - Davis, Watson
  - Davison, Wilburt C
  - Davy, John
  - Day, Mrs. George Parmly
  - Dean Witter & Company
  - De Allende, Maria Angelica
  - De Araújo, Olavo
  - De Benedictis
  - De Bost, Henry
  - De Castro, Josué
  - Decker, Clarence R
  - Decrouez, Mrs. Martha H
  - Dees, Bowen C
  - Defenbacher, D S
  - De Fleury, Comte Serge
  - De Francis, John
  - De Gaetani, Thomas
  - De Goes, Paulo
  - De Jiminez, Zenobia C
  - De Johnson, Berta T
  - De la Balze, Felipe A
  - De la Barbolla, Daniel F Rubin
  - Delacorte, George T, Jr.
  - Delacour, Jean
  - De La Mora, Constancia
  - Del Andrade, E N
  - Delaney, Peter
  - Delano, William Adams
  - Del Rio, Amelia (Mrs. Angel)
  - Del Rio, Angel
  - Del Rio, Martinez
  - Del Rio, Pablo Martinez
  - De la Rocque, Comte Giles
  - De la Torre Bueno, J R
  - Delson, S M
  - De Maria, Mario
  - De Menil, John
  - De Menil, Mrs. John
  - De Montalvo, Marie
  - Dempsey, David
  - Dempsey, Mary H
  - De Muelle, Irma
  - Denman, Leslie Van Ness
  - Denman, Mrs. Leslie. Hopi and Apache rituals Peyote Rituals
  - Dennes, William R
  - Dennis, David H
  - Dennison, Henry S
  - Denny, George V
  - Dent, A W
  - De Onis, Federico
  - De Palencia, Isabel
  - De Pianelli, Edward
  - Derf, N
  - De Rittberg, Theodore
  - Derow, H A
  - Des Granges, Jane
  - Desmond, Mrs. Alice
  - Desmond, Thomas C
  - De Terro, Noel
  - De Tolnay, Charles
  - De Torres, Heloisa
  - Del Torto, Richard
  - De Vane, William C
  - Detwiler, Henry
  - Detwiler, S R
  - Deulofeu, Venancio
  - De Vane, William Clyde
  - De Vane, Mrs. William Clyde
  - Devereaux, Elizabeth
  - Devereaux, Josephs
  - De Vree, Howard
  - Dewey, Kenneth G
  - De Witt, Paul B
  - De Zulueta, Carmen
  - De Zulueta, F
  - D'Harnoncourt, René
  - D'Harnoncourt, Sarah
  - Diamond, David
  - Dick, Alexander
  - Dickey, John
  - Dickson, Anna M
  - Diehl, Charles E
  - Diehl, W C
  - Diet
  - Dietz, Frederick C
  - Dilley, Arthur Urbane
  - Dillon, Douglas
  - Dirksen, Everett McKinley
  - Distler, Theodore A
  - Ditson, Alice M., Fund
  - Diuguid, Lewis H
  - Dixon, Ross
  - Dobzhansky, Theodosius
  - Dockstader, Frederick J
  - Dodds, J W
  - Dodge, Byard
  - Dodge, Cleveland
  - Dodge, Mrs. Cleveland E
  - Dodge, P H
  - Doebler, Charles H, IV
  - Dolcis Shoe Company
  - Dole, Mrs. Arthur
  - Dollard, Charles
  - Domin, Hilde
  - Domus
  - Donaldson, William H
  - Donnell, Patrick
  - Donovan, Gerald
  - Doolittle, J H
  - Doolittle, William B
  - D'Ormesson, Jean
  - Dorn, T E
  - Doro, Edward
  - Dos Passos, John
  - Douchain, Peter
  - Douglas, Lewis W
  - Douglas, Paul H
  - Douglas, William O
  - Douglas-Hamilton, Lady Malcolm
  - Douglass, Robert R
  - Dow, Sterling
  - Dowden, R B
  - Dowling, Margaret
  - Dowling, Robert W
  - Downey, Glanville
  - Drake, K Howard
  - Drápela, Herbert
  - Draper, William F
  - Dreier, Theodore
  - Drever, James
  - Drew, Katherine Fischer
  - Drew, W Harold
  - Dreyer, Louis H
  - Dreyfus, André
  - Drew, Gloria
  - Driggs, Guillermos
  - Drinker, Henry S
  - Drummond, R R
  - Duane, Morris
  - Du Bos, René J
  - Dubridge, Lee A
  - Ducci, Héctor
  - Ducke, Adolfo
  - Duckworth, George E
  - Duell, Charles H
  - Dugand, Armando
  - Durant, Jack D
  - Duggan, Stephen P
  - Duke University Endowment
  - Duke University Press
  - Duling, G Harold
  - Dulles, John Foster
  - Dumbrosky, Andrew
  - Dun, Angus
  - Duncan, R M
  - Dunham, Donald
  - Dunlap, R J
  - Dunlop, John T
  - Dunn, Emmet R
  - Dunn, Ervin S, II
  - Dunn, Gano
  - Dunn, Leslie Clarence
  - Du Pont, Pierre S, 3rd
  - Du Pont Hotel
  - DuPree, A Hunter
  - Duran, Gustavo
  - Durham, Mrs. Colin H
  - Durham, Emily
  - Du Shane, Graham
  - Dussault, M
  - Dusseau, John L
  - Du Vigneaud, Vincent
  - Eagan, Edward P F
  - Eagan, Mrs. Edward
  - Earle, Edward Mead
  - Easby, Dudley T, Jr.
  - Easby, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Easley, Edward H
  - East, Robert A
  - Eastern Air Lines
  - Eastman School of Music
  - Eaton, Allen
  - Eberhart, Sylvia
  - Ebert, Richard C
  - Eckardt, Mrs. Ann
  - Eddy, W A
  - Ede & Ravenscroft
  - Edelstein, Ludwig
  - Edgar, George P
  - Edgecombe, Sally
  - Edgerton, Wallace B
  - Edie, Lionel D
  - Edinger, Tilly
  - Edmonson, J B
  - Education and World Tragedy
  - Edward MacDowell Association
  - Edwards, C D
  - Edwards, Ramón Salas
  - Egeberg, Roger O
  - Egler, Frank E
  - Ehle, John
  - Ehret, George
  - Eichenberg, Fritz
  - Einsiedel, Albert and Luz
  - Eisele, Carolyn
  - Eiseley, Loren
  - Eisenhower, Milton S
  - Eitner, Lorenz
  - Elberg, Sanford S
  - Eldred, Read W
  - Eleutherian Mills Historical Library
  - Elgueta, Manuel
  - Elkinton, J Russell
  - Elkon, Herman
  - Elkus, Albert I
  - Ellinghaus, W M
  - Elliott Bates, Inc.
  - Elliott, George P
  - Elliott, Lloyd H
  - Elliott, Randle
  - Elliott, William Y
  - Ellis, Alma
  - Ellis, Charles D
  - Ellis, John Marshall
  - Ellison, Mrs. Ralph W
  - Ellman, Douglas, and Company
  - Ellman, Richard
  - Elmendorf, John
  - Elsbree, Willard S
  - Else, Gerald F
  - Elton, Lord
  - Elvehjem, Conrad A
  - Ely, Lyn
  - Embree, William Dean
  - Emeneau, Murray B
  - Emergency Shelter, Inc.
  - Emerson, Haven
  - Emery, Ruth
  - Emphasis
  - Engel, Lehman
  - Engle, Donald L
  - Engle, Paul
  - English Academic Children
  - English, Maurice
  - Enters, Angna
  - Erdman, Paul
  - Erdman, Mrs. Paul
  - Erickson, Arvid
  - Erickson, Stephenie (Mrs. James A.)
  - Erim, Kenan T.
  - Ernst, Morris L.
  - Erpf, Armand G.
  - Erskine, Albert de Wolfe, Jr.
  - Erskine, Mrs. Howard M
  - Erskine, John
  - Estol, Horatio
  - Etherington, Edwin D
  - Ethridge, Mark
  - Ettinger, Wilson
  - Eurich, Alvin C
  - Eurich, Nell
  - Europasian Organization
  - Evangelical Press
  - Evans, C N
  - Evans, Clarice
  - Evans, Elwyn
  - Evans, Francis C
  - Evans, Griffith C
  - Evans, Herbert McLean
  - Evans, Len
  - Evans, Orrin B
  - Evans, Richard A
  - Evans, Walker
  - Evarts, John
  - Ewing, James
  - Ewing, Majl
  - Ewing, Maurice
  - Executive Office of the President. Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs Art Section
    See also: Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs
  - Eyssell, Gustave S
  - Fabregat, E Rodriguez
  - Fackenthal, Frank D
  - Fackner, Gladys T
  - Fahs, Charles B
  - Fairbanks, Avard
  - Fairchild, David
  - Fairchild, Henry Pratt
  - Fairmont Park Art Association
  - Falk, Leon
  - Falkner, Judson
  - Fallon, Eduardo
  - Fansler, Roberta
  - Farber, Evan Ira
  - Farias, Raymundo
  - Farill, Juan
  - Farjeon, Herbert
  - Farley, Colvin
  - Farmer, James A
  - Farmers' Museum
  - Farnsley, Charles
  - Farnsley, Mrs. Nancy
  - Farnsworth, Mrs. Anne L
  - Farrar, John
  - Farrar, Straus & Company
  - Farrell, Joseph
  - Farrell, Nancy
  - Farrow, Karl
  - Faulkner, Barry
  - Fausett, Dean
  - Feingold, Jessica
  - Feldman, Eugene
  - Fellowships, Etc.
  - Fels, William C
  - Fenimore BooksStore
  - Fenn, Ellsworth
  - Fernandez, Isabelle
  - Fernandez, Justino
  - Ferrebee, J W
  - Ferreira, Décio Moura
  - Ferreyra, Ramon
  - Ferris, Jeffrey
  - Ferris, Madeleine
  - Ferry, F C
  - Ferry, W H
  - Fidelity and Casualty Company
  - Field, Henry
  - Field, Richard M
  - Field, Robert M
  - Fielding, William J
  - Fieldston Property Owners Assn., Inc.
  - Fife, Robert Herndon
  - Filley, W O
  - Films
  - Finch Junior College
  - Fincke, Benjamin G C
  - Findley, Paul
  - Fink, Herbert L
  - Fink, William B
  - Finkelstein, Louis
  - Finley, David
  - Finley, Robert L
  - Fischer, W W
  - Fisher, Allan G B
  - Fisher, Arden
  - Fisher, Constance E
  - Fisher, Edgar J
  - Fisher, Ernest
  - Fisher, Josephine
  - Fisk, J B
  - Fitzmaurice-Martin, Malachi
  - Flanagan, John T
  - Flanders, Helen Hartness
  - Flanner, Janet
  - Fleming, Frederic S
  - Flexner, Abraham
  - Flexner, Bernard
  - Flexner, Hortense